Stephen Keogh

The Commons, Skerries Road Lusk, North County Dublin

m: 0862072106, t: +353 (1) 8071991

e: stevokeogh@hotmail.com

in ie.linkedin.com/in/stephenkeogh1989

An experienced and adaptable cross skilled IT support technician with five years of experience in both face-to-face and phone-based Mac and PC support. Consistently overachieving on set KPis while passionate about CSAT and delivering a great customer experience.

Experience

Dropbox

Experimental Customer Onboarding Team

September 2019 – Present

Customer onboarding team was created to educate new business teams in all the features of Dropbox.

- Nominated by management to get the onboarding team off the ground.
- · Manage own daily schedule as well as availability.
- Developed new process maps for whole team to optimize each interaction with a customer.
- Talking directly to new team admins educating them on all the features available to them via phone and email.
- Collecting feedback on pain points when onboarding and escalating them to the development team.

Advanced Support Agent, Desktop Application (Client)

Oct 2018 – Sept 2019 (11mos)

- Desktop application support (Client) is working on tickets logged by customers were the Dropbox application is not working correctly.
- Developed technical problem-solving skills by analyzing text files filled with status updates of the desktop app.
- Composed detailed understandable solutions for user to follow to resolve an issue.
- Filed bugs via internal tool to engineering teams to collaborate with them directly towards a solution with detailed cases.
- Communicated every ongoing bug/priority with Client team via Chat tool and email to avoid duplicates.
- Raised ongoing trends on bug which could affect SLA's in CX Team meetings.
- Assigned escalated cases by managers in which a 1to1 would be set up with Business customers.
- Detailed knowledge on all operating systems (Windows, MacOS and Linux) with preferred files systems.
- Trained in new team members on client with overview presentation and reverse shadowing.
- Cross-skilled into different areas of CX such as Mobile, Payments, restorations and the WEB
 application.

Results:

Weekly Quota: 150 tickets a week Achieved: 170+ tickets a week

Customer Call back Team

Apr 2018 - Oct 2018 (6 mos)

- Reached out to call customers that have given a low NPS score for Dropbox to collect feedback on how we can improve Dropbox support.
- Would review tickets to see if all processes were followed by agents.
- Very effective in call handling as also managing email queries. Had the ability to create remote session's while talking to users to resolve these issues.
- · Collected detailed feedback on all areas of support and provided to the development team.

IBM

Service Desk Technical Specialist

Jul 2015 - Apr 2018 (2yrs 10mos)

- Worked effectively as part of a large IT team to ensure effective quick high-quality operation to keep SLA's green.
- Demonstrated attention to detail by accurately writing tickets on each call with their issue and solution.
- Cross skilled on AerLingus, Musgrave, Monument and BGE accounts while managing all accounts simultaneous. Each account has individual systems and processes witch I can quickly understand and provide support for.
- Knowledge on Citrix Receiver for Windows and Citrix Workspace Environment Management
- Processing application and approval form's for hardware allocation E.G: Laptops, Mobiles.

Results:

Target: 40 tickets a day Achieved: 70 tickets a day

Education

CCT College Dublin (2019 – 2020)

Diploma in Python Programming

Institute of Technology Blancherstown (2008 – 2014)

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Engineering

Achievements, Certifications and Interests

- Created a Python script which connects to Zendesk API to reach out to new customers more
 effectively and personal scripts which connects to Dublin bus API for more accurate bus times.
- Achieved employee of the month in IBM for September 2017.
- Passionate soccer player and Astro-League fanatic, currently playing for "Dropbox" in the Inter7's,
 Division 1
- Numerous Soccer titles from DDSL up to AUL Ireland Senior Level football.
- Avid Football and NFL Fan I try to get over to see my teams playing a few times each season
- Technology and gaming: I'm a "geek at heart" and love all things techy and Xbox related

References available on request